bestdietforme.com 2006-12-11

# BestDietForMe.com Free Diet Matching Service to Find the best Weight Loss plan.

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is very important to Marketdata Enterprises, Inc. the owner and operator of bestdietforme.com (collectively, “us”, “we” and “our”). We want you to be comfortable visiting our Website and using our service. Our priority is providing our services to you in a manner that safeguards your privacy. We are a company This Privacy Policy governs our privacy practices in the United States and Canada and explains what information we collect from you, how we collect such information, what we do with such information, what methods we use to protect your information, and the choices you have concerning our use of your information. We ask that you take a moment and read this Privacy Policy carefully. From time to time, we may amend this Privacy Policy and the changes we make will be posted on this web page so that you will always know what information we gather and how we may use that information. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. By using our Website and the services we provide you agree to be bound to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

Please remember that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on our Website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties from whom you request information through our Website. To safeguard your privacy, you should read the privacy policy of each and every website you visit whether as a result of using our Website or otherwise.

**WHO DO I CONTACT IF I HAVE ANY PRIVACY QUESTIONS?**  
If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact us at [privacy@bestdietforme.com](mailto:privacy@bestdietforme.com). Or you may contact us at the address below. 

**WHAT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU IS COLLECTED ON OUR WEBSITE?**  
We collect two types of information: personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information. 

_Personally Identifiable Information_  
Personally identifiable information is information that identifies you or can be used to identify or contact you ("Personally Identifiable Information"). Such Personally Identifiable Information may include your name, address, email address and date of birth. We request Personally Identifiable Information from you when you use our service. We will collect Personally Identifiable Information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. To benefit from our service, we require you to ‘Opt-In’ to the receipt of information from third-party sellers. To provide you with the services we render, we will sell, license, trade or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to third party sellers (as defined below) who will contact you to provide you with services you request through our Website. By way of example, if you choose to receive further information regarding a weight-loss or nutrition service as a result of your responses to our survey, then we will share your Personally Identifiable Information with such third party sellers so that they may contact you directly. Other than as specified in this Privacy Policy, your Personally Identifiable Information will not be disclosed. 

You do not have to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information to visit our Website. However, if you choose to withhold requested information, you will not be able to receive valuable diet and nutrition information from third party sellers that is dependent upon the collection of such information. 

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information_  
When you use our Website or in connection with the services we may make available on our Website from time to time, we may also collect information that by itself cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as demographic information (like age or gender) and health information (like weight and body mass index (“BMI”)) ("Non-Personally Identifiable Information"). Non-Personally Identifiable Information may also include user IP addresses, browser type, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our Website. Non-Personally Identifiable Information is used to help us understand who uses our Website, how our Website is used, and to improve and market our Website in general and our service in particular. 

_Information from Other Sources_  
We may also supplement the information we collect from you with information from other sources to assist us in evaluating and improving our Website and service, to determine your preferences so that we can tailor our service to your needs, and/or to study nutritional, weight loss, behavioral and fitness questions in general. 

**WHERE AND WHEN IS INFORMATION COLLECTED ON OUR WEBSITE (INCLUDING THROUGH THE USE OF COOKIES AND ACTION TAGS)?**  
We will collect information (including Personally Identifiable Information) from you in different manners and at different places and times on our Website. By way of example, when you complete our survey and request information from third party sellers. 

_Using our Website_  
In order to use our Website and to receive the results of your responses to our survey and information from third party sellers we will ask you for information (including Personally Identifiable Information). You will be required to provide us with information (including Personally Identifiable Information) such as name, address, city, state, zip code and email address. This information is used by third party sellers to contact you about their nutrition and diet programs and services. 

_Cookies and Action Tags_  
We also collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information passively using "cookies" and/or "action tags." 

"Cookies" are small text files that are placed on your computer in order to identify (i) your Web browser (ii) the activities of your computer on our Website and (iii) your activity in connection with our advertisements and other marketing and promotional efforts. Cookies may be used to: 

• assist you in using our Website (e.g., to save you time by not having to reenter your name upon each visit to our Website), and   
• allow us to statistically monitor how you are using our Website for purposes of improving our online offerings. 

In the future, as our Website is developed further, we will use cookies and/or action tags to conduct marketing and promotional efforts, tailor certain advertisements to your browser that we think may be of interest to you, or to determine the popularity of certain content. 

In addition to the cookies we place on your computer, in the future, cookies may also be placed on your computer by third parties that we use to display or serve advertisements or to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information in order to provide advertising-related services. We have not designated a third party advertising server company at this time. When we do so we will notify you of our choice to serve our advertisements and the technology they will employ. You do not have to accept cookies to use our Website. However, you may not be able to use certain features or resources of our Website if you do not accept cookies. Although most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, you may reset your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to reject cookies generally. Most browsers offer instructions on how to do so in the "Help" section of the toolbar. 

"Action tags," also known as web beacons or .GIF tags, are a web technology used to help track anonymous website usage information, such as how many times a specific page has been viewed. Action tags are invisible to you, and any portion of our Website, including advertisements, or e-mail sent on our behalf, may contain cookies that are associated with action tags that are located on our Website. Unlike cookies, action tags are not placed on your computer. At this time, we do not use Action tags. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy over time for updates to this section. When we do designate a third party advertising service company we will amend this Privacy Policy and notify you of who we designate, the technology they will employ and give you the information you will need to “opt-out” from their technology. 

Finally, please note that advertisers and other third parties may also use their own cookies or action tags when you click on their advertisement or link to their website from our Website. This Privacy Policy does not govern your use of such third party websites or the privacy practices of third party advertising providers. 

_Log Files_  
We also collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information through our Internet log files, which record data such as user IP addresses, browser types, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our Website. This information may be used to analyze trends, to administer the Website, to monitor our Website's use, and to gather general demographic information. We may link this information to Personally Identifiable Information for these and other purposes such as personalizing your experience on our Website and evaluating our service in general. 

**DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE?**  
No. We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. Our Website and service are not designed for or directed to children under the age of 13. We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13. We urge all parents and/or guardians to participate in their children's exploration of the Internet, and to teach their children about protecting their personal information while online. 

**WHAT DO WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?**  
In general, we use the information collected on our Website to help us understand who uses our Website and how they are using it, to assist you in using our Website, and to improve our Website and service. As a user of our Website and after you "‘Opt-In’" to future communications from third party sellers you will be contacted by such third parties regarding their product and service offerings that may be of interest to you. If you no longer desire for us to share your information with such third parties email us at [unsubscribe@bestdietforme.com](mailto:unsubscribe@bestdietforme.com). After you receive information from third party sellers and if you no longer wish to receive such information please contact each third party seller directly to unsubscribe from their communications. 

We may also use the information gathered on our Website to perform statistical analysis of user behavior, to analyze and evaluate issues relating to nutrition, weight loss, behavior and fitness, or to evaluate and improve our service and to assist those third party sellers in doing same. 

**WHEN DO WE DISCLOSE INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES?**  
Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy or as specifically agreed to by you, we will not disclose any information we gather from you on our Website. 

_Laws and Legal Rights_  
We may also disclose your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with an applicable statute, regulation, rule or law, a subpoena, a search warrant, a court or regulatory order, or other valid legal process. We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information in special circumstances when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms & Conditions, or to protect the safety and/or security of our users, our Website or the general public. 

_Third Parties Generally_  
We may provide to third parties information about you that does not allow you to be identified or contacted, including where such information is combined with similar information of other users of our Website. For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of unique users who visit our Website, the demographic breakdown of the users of our Website, or the activities that visitors to our Website engage in while on our Website. The third parties to which we may provide this information may include potential or actual advertisers, providers of advertising services (including website tracking services), commercial partners, sponsors, licensees, researchers and other similar parties. We will provide third parties with your Personally Identifiable Information only when you ‘Opt-In’ to receive information from these third party sellers.

_Outside Contractors_  
We may employ independent contractors, vendors and suppliers (collectively, "Outside Contractors") to provide specific services and products related to our Website, such as web hosting and developing applications for our Website and e-mail services. These Outside Contractors may sometimes have limited access to information collected on our Website, including your Personally Identifiable Information, in the course of providing products or services to us. Access to your Personally Identifiable Information by these contractors is limited to the information reasonably necessary in order for the Outside Contractors to perform their limited function for us. We also require that these contractors (i) protect the privacy of your Personally Identifiable Information consistent with this Privacy Policy, and (ii) not use or disclose your Personally Identifiable Information for any purpose other than providing us with products or services for which we contracted. 

_Third Party Sellers_  
Through our Website, you have the opportunity to obtain more information regarding certain content, products or services sold through a person or company other than us ("Third Party Sellers"). Third Party Sellers may request that you submit certain information to them in order to purchase their products or services or to obtain additional information from them. You do not need to submit this information or purchase any products or services from Third Party Sellers to access our Website. By choosing to ‘Opt-In’ to receipt of Third Party Sellers information, you affirmatively consent to have your Personally Identifiable Information shared with the Third Party Seller. How such Third Party Seller uses your Personally Identifiable Information will be subject to such Third Party Sellers privacy practices.

_Sale of Business_  
We reserve the right to transfer information to a third party in the event of a sale, merger or other transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of Marketdata Enterprises, Inc. We will notify users of any such transfer through notice on our site and through email. 

**DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLY WHEN I LINK TO OTHER WEBSITES?**  
No. Our Website contains links to other websites not owned or operated by us (for example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, you will likely be taken off our Website to another website). Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites. We encourage you to be aware when our Website links to other websites and to read the privacy policies or statements of each and every website. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by our Website. 

**IS THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT SECURE?**  
We want your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) to remain as secure as possible. We strive to provide secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers through industry-standard techniques. We use Secured Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in transmitting such Personally Identifiable Information over the Internet to our servers. We secure the Personally Identifiable Information you provide on servers located in controlled, secure environments, protected from unauthorized access, use, or alteration. Only employees who need access to your information to perform a specific task or function are granted access to such information. In addition, our employees must abide by this Privacy Policy and are kept up-to-date on security practices. Any employee who violates this Privacy Policy is subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination. 

Notwithstanding the above commitments to protect your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) from loss, misuse or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet. There is also some risk that others could find a way to thwart our security systems. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot insure or warrant the security and privacy of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

**WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE REGARDING THE COLLECTION, DISCLOSURE AND DISTRIBUTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?**   
Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will only use Personally Identifiable Information for the purposes described above or as otherwise disclosed at the time we request such information from you. You must ‘Opt-In’ and give us permission to use your Personally Identifiable Information. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us via postal mail, you may notify us by calling us at 813-931-3900 or by contacting us at the address set out below. 

**CAN I UPDATE OR CORRECT MY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?**  
You can always contact us in order to (1) update or correct your Personally Identifiable Information, (2) change your preferences with respect to communications and other information you receive from us, or (3) delete the Personally Identifiable Information maintained about you on our systems, by contacting us at [info@bestdietforme.com](mailto:info@bestdietforme.com) or at the address set out below. Such updates, corrections, changes and deletions will not have an effect on other information that we maintain, or information that we have provided to third -parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy prior to such update, correction, change or deletion. 

You should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us from our systems. The need to back-up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your Personally Identifiable Information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate. We promise that promptly after receiving your request, all Personally Identifiable Information stored in databases we actively use and other readily searchable media will be updated, corrected, changed or deleted, as appropriate, as soon as reasonably practicable. 

**HOW WILL I KNOW IF THERE ARE ANY CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY?**  
If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this web page so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use Personally Identifiable Information in a manner significantly different from that stated in this Privacy Policy, or otherwise disclosed to you, at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email or otherwise, and you will have a choice as to whether or not we use your Personally Identifiable Information in the new manner. We may also make non-significant changes to our Privacy Policy that generally will not affect our use of your Personally Identifiable Information. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you should not use our Website. 

**WHO DO I CONTACT IF I HAVE ANY PRIVACY QUESTIONS?**  
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or feel that we are not abiding by the terms of our posted Privacy Policy, please contact us as at [ privacy@bestdietforme.com](mailto:privacy@bestdietforme.com) or via postal mail as follows:

Marketdata Enterprises, Inc.  
2807 Busch Blvd. Suite 110  
Tampa, Florida 33618 

BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT USE OUR WEBSITE. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF OUR WEBSITE FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL MEAN THAT YOU ACCEPT THOSE CHANGES.

Last modified September 10, 2004
